Seino, gargal channel, go go go!
Yay!
Yes, that's right, this time we have the Idols here to play with us!
Yay! I'm so excited!
Please introduce yourselves!
Yes, I'm Chiho Ishida from STU48!
Yes, I'm Mai Nakamura, also from STU48!
I'm Eino Yasumi from HKT48!
Please introduce yourself!
For this project, I answered questions while doing gender!
What do you think? Do you usually do gender?
No, I don't!
And today, there is a penalty for using honorifics, so when we are doing gender, we will all be using food!
Sounds fun!
I get it!
You're fast!
Sweets is fast!
Since the members of Idols are here, I'm sure there will be lots of questions about Idols, so the four of us will have fun answering them!
Yes, so let's get right to it, but from here on out, no honorifics!
I don't know why it might not be okay, but I'll start without honorifics.
Let's start!
Who would like to start?
Well, let's start with Chiho-chan.
Then, I'll go first.
Oh, this one too?
That's fast! Chiho-chan.
This one's no good either.
But I just got in.
I guess they'll add more.
Punishment game was out quietly just now.
Raku-san looks happy.
Wait, are you waiting?
I've already said it now, so it's out.
I see.
Thanks.
Well then, let's do Chiho.
Bye-bye.
I'm pulling out.
It's okay at first.
Number 18.
What do you need to become an idol?
This is perfect for Jiho.
Really?
What do you need?
Spirit and perseverance.
That's all.
I think I can handle dancing and singing after I'm done,
If you have the spirit and the guts.
I'm in.
What I think.
You can be who you want to be if you have spirit and guts.
You can be yourself.
Yes, I can.
It's difficult.
Sing casually all the time,
And then, more and more, more and more.
This is a penalty game, so you will have a hard time at the end.
The last one is a sour one at once.
Height.
52.52.
It's.
Oh! A word!
What's that word?
It doesn't say anything.
What's that? Isn't that one of your favorites?
I'm good at it.
I'm good at that.
The guy next to me is a frequent customer.
The customer next door is a frequent rusher.
The customer next door is a frequent customer.
Did you get it?
I couldn't say it, but I could say it.
I did.
I could say it.
What should I do?
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Oh, not at all,
Not at all,
Can I change it?
Oh,
Uh..,
Wait a minute.
Not at all,
I don't know what's going on.
It's not safe.
Not at all,
Wait, wait, wait.
What the hell do you want me to do?
Oh, no, no, no, no,
Wait,
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Did you get it?
Oh, no,
I'm sorry.
I just need a minute of your time.
Uh, 45.
Number 45.
Someone I admire.
Who do you admire?
Well, there are a lot of people.
I mean, I know that there are a lot of people in the group
who pulled us together as a group.
I think I respect Mr. Sasahara the most
I respect him the most.
I think I respect Mr. Sasahara the most.
Yes, Mr. Nakamura, now,
Mr. Nakamura, you have used a lot of youtubers
I know that you have used a lot of youtubers.
You took the most.
That's terrible.
But..,
I respect you.
That's terrible.
I use it unconsciously.I use it unconsciously.
Yeah, it's hard.
It's hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
Number 25.
Number 25,
Oh,
What's your least favorite food?
Wow.
My least favorite food is tomatoes.
Is this the same as Chisato's?
Yes, we found that out yesterday.
That's right.
Hey.
No, thank you,
What a surprise.
Oh, it's number 53.
Number 53,
Wow, I'm going to yell.
Gesture game.
Gesture game?
How hard can it be?
Do something,
You want me to guess?
Yes, that's right.
Yeah.
Okay, then,
Here we go.
Okay.
Can I go one more time?
I'm going.
Okay. - Okay.
What? What kind?
Hint?
Uh, Japanese.
Japanese.
Can I try one more time?
The last one.
What's that?
What?
Uhhh...
Okay, okay.
You got it?
Okay, please.
Okay.
Fireworks.
The correct answer is...
Momotaro.
What?
Mt. Fuji.
Fireworks?
What fireworks?
I don't know.
It all sounds very Japanese.
The correct answer was Momotaro.
So I'm not very good at this.
Hmm.
You're so sweet.Gentle.
I couldn't guess.
I'm sorry
Next.
I was pretty oblivious.
With the sword
The amount of water in the glass.
Who is it now?
Me?
I just used it again.
I'm sorry.
Number 10.
Idols member.
You know what you can do that no one else can?
Uh...
It's hard.
Hmmm...
Um...
Laguhan?
Great Laguhan.
Mmm...
Flexible!
Ooh!
Soft!
I'm a ballet dancer.
Heh.
So I'm good at it.
Wow!
I'm good at it.
Around here.
Oh!
Yes, sir.
Number nine.
What is the name of the coffee shop where the story takes place?
Cafe Milky Way.
What? A coffee shop?
What? It's not a coffee shop?
What?
It's not a cafe Milky Way.
A coffee shop?
A coffee shop.
Oh, a cafe.
A cafe.
I don't know.
I'm really curious.
This way, right?
Okay, let's go.
It's already pretty empty down there.
Number 35.
Sometimes you think you're the only one who's ever been there.
It's hard.
It's definitely hard.
What is it?
Rap?
I don't think so.
No?
Rap?
Okay, rap.
Cool.
Oh, my God, you guys look so much alike.Oh my God, they look so much alike.
Wait a minute.
Wrap.
I'm so confused.
What do you think so far? Who's it gonna be?
Still me?
Chibu, I didn't expect this.
Teru teru teru
I'm scared
Are you okay?
You're good
Jayne Amazing!
You're all so bad at this.
Here we go.
Number 19.
What do you do best when you perform?
What?
What are you particular about when you perform?
I don't have that much acting experience.
I read a lot of scripts.
I think it's important to read a lot of scripts and get to know the characters.
That's a lot of honorifics.
I'm just a normal jane.
I'll be careful.
Yes, you're right.
I just said that.
Okay, next one is my queue.
No.8 What is the character of Mai Nakamura played by Mai Nakamura, who is so good!
Look at her with confidence and look at the camera.
In fact, she is talkative and smiles a lot.
She's not very cautious, and she's a bit of a strawberry.
She's open to everyone!
Applause
I wonder how they'll react.
Well, we haven't even started rehearsals yet.
We're just getting started.
What do you like about the masters?
If he's going to be there...
I think it's easier to take a picture at the edge of the room than in the middle.
Thank you.
It's true.
No.36 What youtube channels do you often watch?
What youtube channels do you watch a lot?
Do you watch it?
I do.
I don't know what it is.
It's a youtube channel about a very old diner run by a grandma and grandpa.
Heh.
It's hard to find a place to watch it.
Please check it out!
It's interesting.
Check it out!
It's funny.
Here comes the last one.
I like the bridge.
I'll beat you here.
I'm sure we can beat him.
If you beat him...Only if you beat him.
What's that?
There's so much in there.
So I can pick one?
Who's your favorite?
Number 28.
What's your favorite recent purchase?
What's the best thing you bought recently?
A bag.
A bag
Do you have it? Recently purchased
Yes?
Recently bought?
I only use honorifics.
Yes?
I bought a washing machine.
It's so big.
I bought one.
I bought a rice cooker.
You know what I was saying?
I'm going to put half the calories on it.
It's so much better.
It's got this thing where you can cut the calories in half.
But it's a pain in the ass.
I don't even cook with it once.
When I have the time
I bought a bread machine
And we use it as a family.
For my mom.
I bought a homemaker
to make bread at home.
They're all appliances.
Appliances.
It's all about home appliances
Well, now that I've defeated the zinger, we're almost at the end of the show, but since the Idols members are all here, I'd like to delve a little deeper into the story of the Idols' upcoming show.
But now that all the Idols members are here, I'd like to go into a little more detail about the stage that Idols is about to start from here.
First of all, Idols is going to perform on stage this time, and we have roles to play, so let's take a look at them one by one.
Could you tell us a little bit about the role you are going to play and the name of the part you are going to play? Please start with Senbon-san.
I will be playing the role of Misora.
Yes, I, Nakamura, will be playing the role of Hoshino.
I, Nana Kamihira, will be playing the role of Tsukie.
I, Kira Yamaguchi, will be playing the role of Yako.
I will be playing the role of an idol from the 80's.
I will be playing two roles, and I will be playing the character of the role I am playing, as well as my own character.
I think Maibi mentioned it earlier, but I haven't mentioned it for years.
Chiho Ishida, what kind of character do you play as Chiho Ishida?
Yes, my character is Chiho Ishida.
When we get to know each other well, she can be rough and independent, but when we meet for the first time, she can be serious and a little catty.
I think she has a character of being serious and a little bit catty, which is exactly the same as my character.
I think he saw right through me.
What is your character like?
Since I was a little girl, my character has been a bifurcated version of Tsukie, the other character I play.
I play this role because I believe in something too much and I am very cautious.
I will also play the role of an idol group from the 80's that we play the other role of.
I will play the role of an 80's idol group who rejects the group as equals.
Equal rejection.Equal rejection.
I can't imagine that.
But I can imagine that you must be very good at it when I see your first idols.
I feel like I'm refusing to be equal to them.
I get it.
It's a disgusting feeling.
I'm going to play the role, and I really like it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm thrilled.
The character I play is cheerful, communicative, and doesn't hold grudges against others, but she actually has a negative side to her,
I'm used to being in a group, and I'm always keeping an open mind.
I think she fits in well.
I wonder if she fits in.
I do think that my cheerful side is a good match for her,
But I've been thinking a lot about how to express my negative side.
I don't think I show it too much.
I don't show it much.
It's amazing.
So, we delved a little deeper into the idol characters,
There is still the Jenga penalty game we played earlier.
Yay!
I wonder who has the most.
Yes, Kyu-chan.
Isn't she very thin?
It's too thin.
I want to add more.
But Nappi is also surprisingly thick.
About the same as Kyu-chan and Jin-chan.
Maybe about the same.
But it's thick.
It's rare. I can't believe these idols are doing this kind of punishment game for us.
So, cheers!
Bon appétit.
Oh!
Yum!
Delicious!
It sure is tasty!
It's good, but it's good.
Yum!
It's good, but it
But it lingers in the throat.
It's true, I'm having a lot of it right now.
What?
It's just not in my throat today.
It's in my throat today.
It stings.
It tastes good.
Yum!
Lastly, I have an announcement to make. The event in which we, the Idols, will perform
Idols Dream Sequence will be held on August 25th and 26th at Shinagawa Interstee Hall.
Yuha and Minami, who are also members of Idols, will perform as special guests.
For more information, please check out the Idols' duplicate page. Thank you for your cooperation.
We would like to thank all the members of Idols for coming as special guests this time.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for watching to the end.
If you like this video, please give it a high rating, subscribe to our channel, or leave a comment.
I want to do it! I want to do it!
Please give it a high rating, subscribe to our channel, and comment.
Thank you very much. Bye bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.Please subscribe to our channel.